DANNY NGUYEN

M: 0434 588 098 | EMAIL: khoa_dang_nguyen@hotmail.com

SUMMARY

I am a self-motivated and enthusiastic university student with 3 years of work experience in a range of different roles. Currently seeking a casual/part-time position that will enable me to continually develop my experience and skills. I believe my highly adaptive and interpersonal skills can contribute positively to the workplace's environment and mission.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Kong Bros Catering

Team Waiter March 2019 – Current

- A position that utilized strong team-work skills, time-management, the ability to work under pressure, and attention to
 detail. This would aid any future positions the ability to think effectively and quickly under pressure is essential for a role
 in the engineering industry.
- Set up, decorate and prepare serving and dining area according to specific directions and layout plan established by the catering manager
- Take orders from customers and timeously serve food and beverages to them
- Do consistent check-ins with patrons to ensure satisfaction and address complaints swiftly
- Answer questions about the menu items and make recommendations when asked
- Assist front-of-house by greeting, seating and thanking customers
- Communicate with kitchen staff directly and via computerized systems to place and follow up on orders

Instant Security Door & Screen

Labourer February 2018 – Current

• This position involved early starts, long hours, and often was in unfavorable weather conditions, thus, it allowed me to develop a disciplined work ethic and a drive for a role I am passionate about.

Tiger's Chang Moo Kwan Taekwondo Academy

Instructor

February 2018 – November 2018

- Part-time role that involved instructing afternoon Taekwondo classes for kids and teenagers. Duties ranged from coordinating drills, teaching technique, and maintenance of the gym.
- A challenging experience that required patience, leadership skills, and communications to ensure everybody was learning, having fun, and keeping safe. The skills developed in this role were invaluable and would transfer well to any future leadership or team based environment.

EDUCATION

The University of Adelaide

Graduating in December 2022

Bachelor of Engineering (Honours) (Mechatronics) with Bachelor of Mathematical and Computer Sciences (Comp Sci Major)

Blackfriars Priory School

South Australian Certificate of Education

- ATAR of 89.96
- All Years High / Highest Honours for yearly academic reports
- Strong presence in the sporting community through being member of the taekwondo, aquatic and badminton teams.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Skills: Proficient in Excel, Word, PowerPoint, C++, MATLAB, Linus, Mac OSX, Windows, Festos, C167, circuit design, Solidworks CAD/Simulation.
- Bilingual; English and Vietnamese
- In my spare time I tutor Year 11 mathematics and enjoy reading, sightseeing and cooking

REFEREES:

Hieu Dang, Manager of Kong Bros. Ph: 0422 190 007

Andy Chiem, Assistant Director of YMCA Woodville Gardens. Ph: 0450 418 209